<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_tile">Atlanta Braves</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">2019 Draft Review</string>
    <string name="article_text">The 2019 MLB Draft is in the books. That means it’s time for the annual draft recap, taking a look at every player the Braves have selected this year.
        If you remember from last year, this is a place to get information on every pick as well as handicapping their odds of signing. That piece can be found at www.talkingchop.com.
        \n\n
        <b>1.Shea Langeliers, C, Baylor</b>
        \n\n
        The Baylor catcher is going to be a defensive star who should be able to add 20 homers a year. I have some question about how much he hits, but there is no question that he will be an elite defender and pitch framer. Some of the comps on him, including my own, include a better hitting Austin Hedges,
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. It was reported that he signed on Sunday for $4M, a full $950k under the slot value.
        \n\n
        <b>1.Braden Shewmake, SS, Texas A&amp;M</b>
        \n\n
        Shewmake isn’t the highest upside pick, but he’s been extremely productive in his three years for the Aggies. Shewmake is a career .322/.378/.488 hitter.
        His biggest concern is his lack of power, as he topped out at 11 homers as a freshman, and has hit that many combined over the next two years. It’s also worth noting many expect him to need to move off short defensively, with a likely home at second or third.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. It’s been announced he signed, and received slot.
        \n\n
        <b>2. Beau Philip, SS, Oregon State</b>
        \n\n
        I admit I didn’t understand this one at the time. I actually liked Philip, but was thinking of him in rounds 6-10 rather than the second round.
        The former JUCO transfer has spent one year at Oregon State and put up a solid .313/.362/.475 line in 39 games while missing some time with injury. Philip has some decent all around tools to go with the projection, but none are plus tools.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Philip came in under slot.
        \n\n
        <b>3. Michael Harris, OF/LHP, Georgia HS</b>
        \n\n
        The Braves started the second day of the draft going the prep route, taking a local kid who could have been drafted on Day 2 as a hitter or a pitcher. Harris prefers to hit and it sounds like he will get his first shot as a pro in that role.
        Harris is an athletic outfielder with plenty of raw power potential, but also a prospect with plenty of swing and miss. On the mound he has a fastball up to 93 MPH from the left side and a promising curve as part of his three pitch mix. Most teams seem to prefer him on the mound, so that fall back if he doesn’t hit enough is always an option.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Harris is a Brave and should start in the GCL.
        \n\n
        <b>4. Kasey Kalich, RHP, Texas A&amp;M</b>
        \n\n
        Coming into the draft I would have ranked Kalich as one of the top five pure reliever prospects in the draft- guys who are already relievers and will only be relievers going forward. He’s only a draft eligible sophomore who spent just one year with the Aggies after coming from JUCO. Kalich racked up 12 saves with a 14.3 K/9 rate and is a guy who should move quickly though the minors. I don’t see Kalich as a future closer, but he has setup man upside with a fastball up to 95 MPH and a solid slider. For those wondering, I do not expect him to reach Atlanta in 2019.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Kalich has signed.
        \n\n
       <b>5. Stephen Paolini, OF, Connecticut HS</b>
        \n\n
        Stephen Paolini came out of no where to be the Braves pick. No one had many notes on him, including myself. I had circled his name from an event report last fall that was extremely positive, but hadn’t heard anything more until the Braves drafted him. He’s got a promising body for projection, a swing built for power, and is a plus runner. The adjustment from Connecticut high school competition to pro ball is going to be a large adjustment, but this kid is very toolsy.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Paolini came in overslot, showing the Braves had to really believe in his talent to use such a high pick on him and then go overslot to get him.
        \n\n
        <b>6. Tanner Gordon, RHP, Indiana</b>
        \n\n
        Another JUCO arm that went to D1 this year is Gordon, following the same path as Kalich. Gordon is a little different as a bigger bodied(6’5”, 215) starter. Gordon, who made 14 starts this spring with a 3.35 ERA, 0.97 WHIP, and 9.6 K/9, was actually a JUCO teammate of Trey Riley last year before heading to Bloomington. Gordon is a guy with a 94 MPH fastball that he gets downhill plane on to force ground balls, so he’s more of a pitch to contact guy than a strikeout pitcher.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Gordon will be starting the year in Danville.
        \n\n
        <b>7. Darius Vines, RHP, CSU Bakersfield</b>
        \n\n
        After being drafted in each of the past two drafts, Darius Vines finally went high enough to sign this year. The lanky right hander has a four pitch mix and throws strikes. He’s got a very promising curve, and really has three average to slightly above pitches in his arsenal. In his only season in D1, he managed 12.1 K/9. It is also worth noting that the teams who took chances late in the past two drafts are the Astros and Cubs.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Vines came in a little under slot value.
        \n\n
        <b>8. Ricky DeVito, RHP, Seton Hall</b>
        \n\n
        If you look at the stuff alone, Ricky DeVito probably goes about 4-5 rounds sooner. The 2018 Big East Pitcher of the Year with a 1.88 ERA and 1.03 WHIP in 12 starts struggled a bit this year, pitching to a 3.92 ERA and 1.62 WHIP as he struggled at times with his command. DeVito has always had some inconsistencies with his command, but he’s got a heavy sinking fastball he runs up to 94 MPH and promising pitches in both the change and curve.
        It’s possible that DeVito has a pair of future plus pitches and a third that could be average. That’s the recipe for a middle of the rotation starter should he be able to command it a little better- something maybe a slight mechanical tweak could help.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. DeVito came in slightly overslot.
        \n\n
        <b>9. Cody Milligan, UTL, Kansas JUCO</b>
        \n\n
        Cody Milligan landed in JUCO from Oklahoma State and had a very productive season for a team which made an impressive postseason run. Milligan hit .453 with five homers, 63 RBI, 30 for 30 in steals, and 89 runs scored in 61 games played. Milligan is a solid hitter and a guy with a plus run tool to go with a little more power than what he showed this season, adding 18 doubles and 9 triples to his extra base hit totals.
        He actually caught this year and has some potential in the outfield, though many see a future second baseman. If Milligan can be a future catcher his value rises, and it would already be high due to his defensive versatility.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Milligan was a little overslot and will be headed to Danville.
        \n\n
        <b>10. Brandon Parker, OF, Mississippi JUCO</b>
        \n\n
        Brandon Parker is a solid hitter with some real power potential, but also a guy with swing and miss. He’s one of the higher upside guys on Day 2 because of his bat, but he’s also a bit of a lottery ticket because he’s going to need to prove he can hit.
        \n\n
        Odds of Signing: SIGNED. Parker is delivered already and will be in Danville. </string>
</resources>
